uquery.com 2009-04-30

# PageGlimpse.com - Privacy Policy

RADSense Software takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

### Information Collection and Use

When you register for services provided by RADSense Software we collect personal information, aggregate information on what pages users access or visit and information volunteered by the users (such as surveys information). RADSense Software does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances 

It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of  Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if RADSense Software or PageGlimpse is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, RADSense Software will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

RADSense Software uses collected information for the following general purposes: to contact you, improve products and services, billing, identification and authentication, research. 

### Cookies

RADSense Software may set and access RADSense Software cookies on your computer

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Cookies are required to use the services provided by RADSense Software.

We might use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies.

### Changes

RADSense Software may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [privacy@PageGlimpse.com](mailto:privacy@pageglimpse.com) or by mail at: RADSense Software Inc., 3319 Covered Bridge Dr E, Dunedin, FL USA
